eveek.com 2008-12-17

# Free Blackberry Downloads | Themes | Wallpapers | Ringtones | Forum - Privacy

Information collection and use   
From time to time, you will be asked to submit personal information about yourself (e.g. name and email address etc) in order to receive or use services at eVeek. Such services include newsletters, competitions, "Alert Email", live chats, message boards and eVeek membership, which you will receive directly from us at eVeek. You can easily subscribe or unsubscribe to newsletters and other notifications you may receive from eVeek by going to your account preferences when you are logged in (My Account – Settings) 

By entering your details in the fields requested, you enable eVeek and its service providers to provide you with the services you select. Whenever you provide such personal information, we will treat that information in accordance with this policy. Our services are designed to give you the information that you want to receive. eVeek will act in accordance with current legislation and aim to meet current Internet best practice. 

Information on visitors   
During the course of any visit to eVeek, the pages you see, along with something called a cookie, are downloaded to your computer (see point 3 for more details on this). Most, if not all, websites do this, because cookies allow the website publisher to ascertain whether the computer (and probably its user) has visited the site before. This is done on a repeat visit by checking to see, and finding, the cookie left there on the last visit. 

Any information that is supplied by cookies can help us to provide you with a better service and assists us to analyze the profile of our visitors. For example: if on a previous visit you went to the mobile wallpaper section, then we might find this out from your cookie and highlight wallpapers on a second visit. 

What is a cookie?   
When you enter a site your computer will automatically be issued with a cookie. Cookies are text files that identify your computer to our server. Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. Many sites do this whenever a user visits their site in order to track traffic flows. Cookies themselves only record those areas of the site that have been visited by the computer in question, and for how long. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalized services cannot then be provided to that user. 

NB: Even if you haven't set your computer to reject cookies you can still browse our site anonymously until such time as you register for eVeek services. 

Use and storage of your personal information   
When you supply any personal information to eVeek (e.g. for competitions, eVeek Community services or eVeek membership) we have legal obligations towards you in the way we deal with that data. We must collect the information fairly, that is, we must explain how we will use it and tell you if we want to pass the information on to anyone else. In general, any information you provide to eVeek will only be used within eVeek and by its service providers. It will never be supplied to anyone outside eVeek without first obtaining your consent, unless we are obliged or permitted by law to disclose it. Also, if you post or send offensive or inappropriate content anywhere on or to eVeek or otherwise engage in any disruptive behavior on eVeek, and eVeek considers such behavior to be serious and/or repeated, eVeek can use whatever information that is available to it about you to stop such behavior. This may include informing relevant third parties such as your employer, school or e-mail provider about the content and your behavior. 

We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as you use the service you have requested, and remove it in the event that the purpose has been met, or, in the case of you no longer wish to continue your status as a eVeek member. For safety reasons, however, eVeek may store messaging transcript data (including message content, member names, times and dates) arising from the use of eVeek Community services for a period of six months. Where personal information is held for people who are not yet registered but have taken part in other eVeek services (eg competitions), that information will be held only as long as necessary to ensure that the service is run smoothly. We will ensure that all personal information supplied is held securely, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. 

If you are notified on eVeek that your information may be used to allow eVeek to contact you for "service administration purposes", this means that eVeek may contact you for a number of purposes related to the service you have signed up for. For example, we may wish to provide you with password reminders or notify you that a particular service has been improved or suspended.   
  
Access to your personal information   
You have the right to request a copy of the personal information eVeek holds about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. (There is a small charge for such administration requests.) 

Contact Information   
All enquiries regarding our privacy policy should be sent to our email: support@eveek.com
